YuriAvagyan

Email:

yura372554@gmail.comTel:

+37455480024

About Me

I am a talented Front-end developer with 3+ years of experience in various types of projects. I am a problem solver, and any difficulty I take as a challenge. Teaching developed my soft skills and made myself a good team player.Iam good at communication and an easy-going person.

Experience

Tidepool Labs Europe – Dec 2021 - Present

Full Stack Developer

- Developing Learning Platform using React.js (Redux/Context hooks), Node.js
- Developing OBSD management platform using JavaScript (React.js/Node.js)

Be.next Software Company – Jul 2021 – Jun 2022, Yerevan, Armenia.

Frontend Developer

- Working on a logistics CRM system. Stack: React.js, Redux, Cypress, Material UI.

Fuse8 Online – Oct 2020 – Jul 2021

Front-end Developer

- Developing optimized and highly responsive websites using React.js, Redux, Typescript, andother Front-end libraries and frameworks.
- Working on various projects like CRM systems and E- Commerce

NWS Lab - Jul 2019 - Oct 2020

Front-end Developer

- Working as a front-end developer in an outstaff company.
- Worked on many projects using relevant and modern front-end technologies.
- Mentoring junior developers and interns.

Freelancer – Jan 2020 – Apr 2021

Front-end Developer

- Working mostly on small tasks and bug fixes, doing more UI development using HTML5 and SCSS.
- My first steps as a Software Engineer.

KRKAPharmaceuticals – Sep 2017 – Aug 2018

ITAssociate

- Maintenance of Software and Hardware.
- Maintenance of Servers, Switches and Routers and other office hardware.
- Management of local CRM System InfoZoom.

Skyeng - Mar 2020 - Nov 2021

English Teacher

- Teaching English on one of the most popular online learning platform for students from CIS.
- Teaching as hobby and part-time

Education

Russian Armenian State University

Sep 2010 – Jul 2014, Yerevan, Armenia

Applied Mathematics and Informatics, Bachelor degree

Yerevan State Linguistic University after V. Brusov

Sep 2017 – Aug 2018, Yerevan, Armenia

Chinese language and cultural studies, Post graduate course

Languages

Armenian – Native

English – Proficient, TESOL 120

hoursRussian - Native

Chinese – Intermediate

Skills

Typescript / JavaScript / React.js / Next.js / HTML5 / CSS / SCSS / Styled Components / Node.js / Headless CMS / Version Control / NoSQL / SQL